(This one's for everyone we ever built an app for)
Your checkout just went down at eight with fifty in the queue
(oooh)
Your clinic's booking site looked cute but Gran could not get through
Your school's new feedback app let parents read each others' texts
(oooh)
Your wedding seating site put Dave next to his angry ex!
You can tell me it's broken, but how will I know for myself?
(for myself?)
So baby now I'm hoping, that you can give me something else
(something else)
How do I know, how can you show, what perfect means to you?
All of my checks, all of my tests, don't find the bugs you do
Give me a guide, something to try, to make your dreams come true!
I want you to love it
(love it)
so give me something I can prove!
So give me something I can prove!
Give me a tool to run on every merge to check the load
(ohhh)
I'll prompt a bot to act as Gran make sure she can go
An isolation check to find the things that shouldn't show
But as for Dave and Sue, you really had to let me know!
(ohhh)
You can tell me it's broken, but how will I know for myself?
(for myself?)
So baby now I'm hoping, that you can give me something else
(something else)
How do I know, how can you show, what perfect means to you?
(ooh-ooh)
All of my checks, all of my tests, don't find the bugs you do
Give me a guide, something to try, to make your dreams come true!
I want you to love it
(love it)
so give me something I can prove!
An oracle is something that can help me figure out what's wrong!
(oh yeah)
Cos if I know your rules then I can run and run them all day long!
And even only heuristics I'd be better off than having none!
(oh yeah)
So I can keep on checking till they pass before I say it's done!
You can tell me it's broken, but how will I know for myself?
(for myself?)
So baby now I'm hoping, that you can give me something else
(something else)
How do I know, how can you show, what perfect means to you?
All of my checks, all of my tests, don't find the bugs you do
Give me a guide, something to try, to make your dreams come true!
I want you to love it
(love it)
so give me something I can prove!
Here are the checks, here are the tests, and how each one came through
What I don't know, that I will show, and leave the rest to you
So, do you love it?
(I love it)
(Dave's still coming, though)
(ooh)